Guide to the Samuel Halperin Puck and Judge cartoon collection, 1879-1903 MS2121
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Samuel Halperin Puck and Judge cartoon collection
1879-1903
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Halperin, Samuel
MS2121
11 Linear Feet
This collection contains nineteenth century political cartoons. The collection includes illustrations from issues of "Puck" for the years 1879-1903 and illustrations of "Judge" for the years 1887-1900. Undated illustrations for both magazines are also included. The subject matters of these illustrations are broadly popular culture, history, journalism, and politics.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated by Samuel Halperin.
Historical or Biographical Note
Both "Puck" and "Judge" were weekly magazines during the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries. "Puck" was founded by Joseph Keppler, a Viennese immigrant to the United States. The staff included, at various times, artists such as F. Graetz, Karl Elder von Stur, Frederick Opper, James A. Wales, Bernard Gilliam, Eugene Zimmerman, Louis Dalrymple, C.J. Taylor, Frank A. Nankivell, Louis M. Glackens, J.S. Pughe, and Joseph Keppler, Jr. "Judge" was founded by former "Puck" illustrator James A. Wales, who sold the magazine in 1885 to William J. Arkell. Arkell managed to lure Bernard Gilliam from "Puck" and made him a full partner at "Judge." By the first World War, news magazines like "Puck" and "Judge" were unable to compete with the demands and popularity of the daily newspaper.
[the following book was used to prepare this note: "The Ungentlemanly Art." by Stephen Hess and Milton Kaplan]
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains nineteenth century political cartoons. The collection includes illustrations from issues of "Puck" for the years 1879-1903 and illustrations of "Judge" for the years 1887-1900. Undated illustrations for both magazines are also included. The subject matters of these illustrations are broadly popular culture, history, journalism, and politics.
This collection was donated by Dr. Samuel Halperin in 1995.
Collection Organization
Organized into three series: Illustrations from "Puck", Illustrations from "Judge," and Loose pages from Puck and Judge
Collection note
Formerly Graphic Coll #10. The following biography is about the donor and is from the original finding aid: Dr. Samuel Halperin, who received his doctorate in Political Science from Washington University (St. Louis) in 1956, has held a variety of leadership positions in academia, the federal government, and non-profit organizations. As a congressional Fellow of the American Political Science Association, he worked on U.S. Senate and House of Representatives committees that dealt with major education legislation (1960-61). As Director of the U.S. Office of Education's Office of Congressional Relations and, later, as Assistant U. S. Commissioner of Education for Legislation, he participated in development and passage of such significant measures as the Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965 and the Higher Education Acts of 1963 and 1965. In 1966, Dr. Halperin joined the Office of the Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare where, as Deputy Assistant Secretary under Secretaries John W. Gardner and Wilbur J. Cohen, he continued work as an executive branch he was twice awarded HEW's Superior Service Award lobbyist" for passage of scores of Great Society measures in education and the social services. For these efforts
Politics and government; Journalism; Political cartoons; Popular culture; Wales, James Albert; Keppler, Udo J.
- Illustrations from "Puck", 1879-1903; MS2121 Series 1; 2 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains nineteenth century political cartoons for the years 1879-1903. The subject matters of these illustrations are broadly popular culture, history, journalism, and politics.
  - "The New Exodus." Sambo:-`Now, boss, how you like it you' self?' ", 04/16/1879 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Captain Williams and His Patent-Safety `Sword of Damocles.' ", 04/23/1879 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "How to Settle It.: The Only Fair Way to Decide the Claims of the two Nations.", 04/30/1879 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Les Enfants Terribles.", 09/20/1879 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Political Baby Farming:-How to Tell'Tother From Which.", 10/15/1879 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Do Not Fear, We'll Protect You!", 11/19/1879 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "The Irish Milch Cow.-Parnell Next!", 12/31/1879 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Too Many Drivers", 01/21/1880 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Uncle Sam With His Hands Full.", 02/04/1880 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Will the Cat Do It?", 02/18/1880 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "A Russian Bath-Imperial Style.", 03/03/1880 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "In Bad Company.-The Projected Monument to Washington in Wall Street.", 03/10/1880 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Talmage's Dollar Subscription.-Puck is the First Man In.", 03/17/1880 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Five Dishonest Politicians Have Been Sent to the Penitentiary in Pennsylvania.-If This System Were Generally Adopted, Our Legislative Halls Would Look Pretty Much as Above.", 05/05/1880 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Beecher As A Political Sport."Republican Party:-I must decline your escort, sir. My reputation is quite bad enough already.", 06/23/1880 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "H. Bergh's Influence on Uncle Sam.-No Bull Fight!", 09/01/1880 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Asking Too Much."Jewell:-"Now, Mr. Conkling, for Heaven's sake, don't speak entirely about the party-do give poor Garifeld a kind word-he needs it.", 09/08/1880 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Last Bather."Close of the Bathing Season at Manhattan Beach., 09/15/1880 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Love A La Mode in Indiana."W. H. English (to Democratic Party): `You wouldn't deceive an unprotected politician-do you love me for Myself or my gold?', 09/22/1880 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "He Toots for Garfield and Drums for Grant.", 10/06/1880 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "In the 10/Storm.-"Faith-an' it Leaks!", 10/20/1880 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "We Are Glad We Got You In!", 11/03/1880 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "The One Happy Democrat.", 11/10/1880 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "The Retort Courteous." Judge Davis:-`You have forgotten that a Politician MAY be a Gentleman!' A.S. Hewitt: `You have forgotten that a Judge MUST NOT be a Politician!', 11/24/1880 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "The Three 'Dis-Graces.'" A Suggestion for a Monument to the Three Bosses of New York, Brooklyn and Philadelphia., 12/01/1880 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Puck's Conception of Mr. Bergh's Steam Flogging Machine.", 12/08/1880 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "The Wild-Cat Mining Swindle.", 1880 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "A Big Fire For an Old Woman to Put Out.", 01/05/1881 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Reorganization of the Democratic Party." The Tammany Healers Are Equal to the Emergency., 01/12/1881 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "English `Lords' and American Loons.", 01/12/1881 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "LEFT.", 01/19/1881 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "The Marriage Ceremony.", 01/19/1881 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Anything to Keep Him Afloat Till 1884.", 01/26/1881 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "False Modesty.", 02/16/1881 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "America's Revenge." Puck to English Society:-"Well, what do you think of 'Foreign Fortune Hunters'?, 02/23/1881 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Garfield's Bond of Friendship for the Unfriendly Senators.", 03/02/1881 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "At Last He Has a White Man to Deal With.", 03/09/1881 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - "The Distressing Failure of the Brooklyn Revival Business.", 03/30/1881 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "The Dirt Barricade in New York."`Down With its Defenders!', 04/13/1881 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Waiting.", 04/20/1881 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "Disturbing the Neighbors.", 04/20/1881 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - "A Narrow Escape.", 04/27/1881 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "Home, Sweet Home!"("Lay Low, Alexander a bomb is coming!"), 05/04/1881 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "The Bill Butchers at the Albany Slaughter-House.", 05/04/1881 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "The Operation of the Proposed New Code." Governor Cornell:-`I think this man does need a little Reduction.', 05/11/1881 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - "Chester A. Arthur, Vice-President of the U.S., and Political Runner.", 06/01/1881 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - "Now We Have Whipped All Creation!", 06/08/1881 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "The Food of Our Youth.", 09/21/1881 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "Puck's Perplexing Position-Between Two Evils."Puck.-"Well, I want to be an Anti-Monopolist; but not if that is one!", 10/12/1881 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - "Where Justice Will Have to Look for Jurors Who Have Not Formed an Opinion in the Guiteau Case.", 10/26/1881 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - "The Pleasures of a Political Job.", 10/26/1881 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - "A Way Out Of President Arthur's Dilemma." General Grant:-`Don't be Troubled if a few fellows do decline. Here are some friends of mine who never refuse.', 11/02/1881 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - "Our Perennial Pauper." `What! Begging Again?', 12/14/1881 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - "Waiting for Each Other's Death.", 12/21/1881 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - "The Path of Duty.: Star-Routers."Star-Routers:-`Be rul'd, you shall not go!'Hamlet-Arthur:-`I say, away! Go on, I'll follow thee!', 12/28/1881 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - "The Fiddle and the Bow."`A Picture of Municipal Harmony in New York.', 01/11/1882 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - "IT'S NO USE!", 01/18/1882 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - "Circumstances Alter Cases!"British Lion-:`Well, I'll be blowed if that greedy Yankee Eagle hain't trying to spread himself all over Hamerica!', 02/08/1882 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - "Their Only Hope-The Great `Patience' Candidate." Twenty love-sick maidens we, Love-sick all against our will, Two years hence we may not be Quite such love-sick maidens still., 02/15/1882 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - "Shipwrecked Patriotism."Uncle Sam at Sea:-`It's Washington's Birthday, and I want to decorate, but-ahem-well-just lend me the loan of your mast, will you?', 02/22/1882 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - "The Living President's Tribute to the Dead President.", 03/08/1882 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - "Arthur's Awkward 'White Elephant.'""How shall I ever get rid of him? It won't do for me to have him on my hands in 1884!", 03/15/1882 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - "Fallen Into Bad Hands.", 1882 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - "Hopelessly Bound to the Stake.", 08/15/1883 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - "The Cave of Despair.", 08/29/1883 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - "The Two Dromios." American Cowboy to British Nobleman (Villard Variety):-"Methinks, thou art my mirror!", 10/10/1883 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - "In a Critical Condition." N.C. Physician:-"You have talked the baby to death, madam; it will require great care to keep him alive until the 6th of November.", 10/31/1883 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - "The Death-Watch.-The Execution Postponed.", 11/14/1883 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - "The Prodigal's Return.-A Cold Reception."Hard-hearted Father:-"I am sorry, William, but I can't kill this fatted calf for any played-out Re-adjuster like you!", 11/21/1883 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - "Bismarck's Boost."The Uhlan King:-"I'm taller than you, now!", 11/28/1883 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - "He Missed the Chair, But He Has the Floor.", 12/05/1883 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - "A Weak Combination Suspension Bridge.", 12/26/1883 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - "The Slush Will Have to Stay."Buckner:-"Not just now-I'll see you later!", 01/02/1884 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - "Make Him Harmless!", 02/20/1884 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - "Look Before You Eat-And see if you can discover an unadulterated food.", 03/12/1884 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - "Spoiling Their Calculations.", 04/30/1884 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - "Drowning In His Own `Pool.'", 06/04/1884 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - "Me And Jack.", 07/02/1884 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - "They Can Not Stop the Wheel.", 07/23/1884 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - "Tammany Throws Away Its `Butt,' And the Monopoly Bootblack Picks It Up.", 09/24/1884 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - "Out of a Job Once More!", 11/5/1884 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - "Kik-kik-cock-a-doodle doo! Mr. Kelly, how are YOU?", 11/12/1884 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - "Whitelaw Reid Refuses to Accept the New York Senatorship.""I cannot marry you, pretty maid!""Nobody axed you, sir!" she said.(2 copies), 12/03/1884 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - "Since He Cannot Sail the Ship, He Tries to Sink It."(2 copies), 12/10/1884 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - "Squeezed Dry."A Lemon That Will Never More Contribute to the Patronage Bowl., 12/17/1884 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - "Puck's Hint For `Hospital Sunday.'", 12/24/1884 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - "The Knight of the Wind-Bag Enters the Senatorial Field.", 12/31/1884 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - "The `Busted' Side-Show.""The country is full of wrecked theatrical troupes walking home."-Daily Paper., 1884 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - "The Decline of Italian Opera in New York.-Will It Have To Go A-Begging?", 1884 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - "Our Mutual Friend.", 01/07/1885 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - "The Senatorial Puppet Show."General Reproduction of the Rebellion, and Terrific Combat between General Sherman and Jeff Davis!!-Joe Hawley, Manager%32882017677512, 01/21/1885 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - "Grand Triumph Of Brains Over `Boodle'!", 01/28/1885 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - "The Dynamiter's False Friends."They Liked Him Before the Election-They Disown Him Now., 02/04/1885 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - "The Tail Of A Tail.", 02/18/1885 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - "The Old Lion And the Ass."General Rosecrans, (Dem., of California) thought that General Grant's reputation had been exaggerated and misrepresented, and when history came to be written, it would be pared down to very different dimensions.-Debate on the Grant Retirement Bill in the House, Feb. 16th, 1885., 02/25/1885 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - "Here's a health to the Mugwumps, who helped in the strife, And have made this the happiest day of my life!", 03/04/1885 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - "Help Refused.", 03/11/1885 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - "President Cleveland And His Cabinet.", 03/11/1885 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - "An Uneven Game."The Russian Rapscallion has no windows of his own, and he can afford to throw stones at the house of Respectable Briton., 04/29/1885 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - "A Flirtation That May Lead to Serious Results In the Fall."He [John Kelly] will again be drawn into the vortex of politics; and it is in his nature to lead and not to follow.-New York Tribune., 07/29/1885 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - "The Gospel Of the Knights Of Labor.""We work not selfishly for ourselves alone, but extend the hand of fellowship to all mankind."-Mr. Powderly, at Richmond., 10/13/1886 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - "The Dying Song of the Tammany Swan.", 10/20/1886 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - "A Useless Formality.-Will-Making In Our Modern Time."Testator.-Being of sound mind and body, I give and bequeath-Chorus of Will-Breakers.-Ha, ha, ha!, 11/17/1886 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Christmas 1886. "The Portrait Of Mrs. Cleveland." (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - "The Last of the New Years' Callers.", 1886 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - "Our Senatorial Gordon Cumming."British Lion.-It's fortunate for me that the ocean is between us., 02/09/1887 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - "Shake!" "Don't let us quarrel over a little thong like Schnaebeles.", 05/04/1887 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - "Mutual Adoration.", 07/06/1887 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - "A Galileo With A Difference." Galileo was imprisoned for upholding his theories; and we prophesy that Dr. McGlynn's notions will land him in the Board of Alderman., 07/20/1887 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - "More Kettle Than Dog.", 07/27/1887 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - "Spots On the Sun.", 08/03/1887 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - "Getting Rid of the Spoils System Deadwood."G.W. Curtis.-You don't quite keep up with me, Mr. Cleveland.Grover Cleveland.-You have got the easy end of the job, Mr. Curtis; but I mean to get there, all the same., 08/17/1887 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - "As Others See Us" Democratic Party.-Ahem! There seems to be a leak somewhere in your house. G.O.P.-By the way, neighbor, have you caught onto the little conflagration in your rear?, 10/05/1887 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - "Grand Calithumpian Serenade Tendered to the Prohibition Party by the Convention of the German Societies.", 10/12/1887 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - "The Persistent Suitor."Chorus of Wooers Outside.-Why don't he give it up and let us fellows have a show?, 10/26/1887 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - "Drop Your `Nicholl' In, And See the Hands of Justice Work.", 11/02/1887 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - "Two More `Brilliant Americans' For the Prince of Wales to Meet.", 11/09/1887 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - "A Big Balance in His Favor."Puck.- But don't let it occur again!, 11/16/1887 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - "Rushing to Their Own Destruction.", 11/23/1887 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - "The Graveyard Orator." John Sherman. To arms! To arms! The War ain't half over yet!, 11/30/1887 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - "The Countryman and the Snake.", 11/30/1887 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - "Anything to Please Comstock."Monsieur Cabanel (painting his next great picture for the New York market).-I wonder if Comstock will object to this?, 12/07/1887 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - "An Outside Ally.", 12/21/1887 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - "Sincerity."Blaine.-I've retired, William, (so far as it is in my power to so;) but if a message arrives from Chicago, let me know, and I'll get right up!, 03/07/1888 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - "The Progress of Two Booms.", 06/13/1888 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - "The Bigger the Bar'l, the Smaller the Man."A Study of Republican Presidential Possibilities., 06/20/1888 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - "The Grand Old Elephant."Manager Platt (of the Pivotal State).-Here! Look Lively! Get up and dance for monopoly and high tariff!, 06/27/1888 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - "The New Sign.", 07/18/1888 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - "Midsummer Puck", 07/18/1888 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - "They Never Speak As They Pass By.", 08/01/1888 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - "The Tail-End of the Republican Presidential Procession.", 08/22/1888 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - "The Champion of the Protected Robbers."The Greatest Living Statesman.-Stand back! Trusts are private affairs, with which neither President Cleveland nor any private citizen has any particular right to interfere!, 08/29/1888 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - "The Greatest American Statesman.-How He Studied the Condition of the English Laborer.", 09/05/1888 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - "Hopeless and Helpless."Puck.-What are you doing down there?Chorus of Republican Senators.-Trying to put Cleveland in a hole!, 10/03/1888 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - "A Hint From Our Ancestors."They Nailed the Wheat Cornerers of the Middle Ages to the City Hall Door, and distributed their Spoils Among the People. (2 copies), 10/24/1888 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - "In Bad Company."But, even after his latest and worst spree, we think he may be reformed., 12/12/1888 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - "The Proper School for Anarchists."Put them in stocks and make them read the Constitution-and let later arrivals take warning., 1888 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - "The Favored Guest.", 02/20/1889 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - "Puck's Midsummer Train-Boy.", 07/16/1890 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Midsummer Puck, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - "The Peeping Toms of the Camera.", 07/15/1891 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Puck Midsummer Number, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - "A Sample Case of Pension Fraud."And there are more than 100,000 others just like it., 08/09/1893 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - "Rough on the Eagle!", 08/23/1893 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - "No Rioters Need Apply!"Honest Laborer(to Anarchist Agitator).-Help you to destroy law and order?-not much!-and your stories that we are starving are all false!, 09/06/1893 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - "A Parallel Case."Miss La Salle(of Chicago).-I hope you don't believe all you read and hear about Chicago divorces? Miss Tremont(of Boston).-Of course not, dear; we're not so silly.Miss La Salle.-To be sure. I suppose you don't take any more stock in it than we do in Bostonians' professions about being so cultured., 09/11/1893 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - "A Celtic Cinderella.", 1893 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - "A Joke That Went Too Far.", 1893 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - "A Relic of the Dark Ages." John Bull.-Roseberry says he can be mended, but I guess he'd better be ended., 12/12/1894 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - "His Battle-Ground." Where Our Bloodthirsty Jingo Will Be Found When A Real War Comes., 12/11/1895 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - "A Puzzle."How Can McKinley Satisfy Ohio, And Still Have a Little Patronage Milk Left for Other Patriots of the Country?, 01/20/1897 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - "Finishing Touches.", 1903 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - "One Advantage.", 1903 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - "The Adulteration of Food.", undated (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - "The Alchemist of the Past, and the Alchemist of the Present.", undated (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - "All in the Same Boat."The Leaders of the inharmonious Labor Parties are agreed on one point- that the Labor Mule has got to do the pulling., undated (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - "The American Sphinx.", undated (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - "And There He Will Stick!""John Sherman has put his foot on the first round of the ladder that leads to the Presidency."-Phila. Call., undated (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - "Another Big Thing- The Married Men's Lodge-Night Hook-and-Ladder Cab Co.- No More Latch-Keys Needed.", undated (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - "Another Blind for the Biddies.- The Dynamiters' New Device.", undated (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - "Attention, Saloon-Keepers!"How your bar-rooms may be kept closed on Sunday, and your customers be taken care of at the same time. (2 copies), undated (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - "A Bad Break for the Republican Sheep."Shepherd Cleveland.- Well, if they well leave the good, safe road they have traveled for long, there is no help for them!, undated (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - "Better Not Vaccinate Than Vaccinate With Impure Virus.", undated (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - "Boss Kelly Eats the Leek.""By this leek, I will most horribly revenge! I eat, and eke I swear. All hell shall stir for this!"-King Henry V., Act V., Sc. I., undated (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - "Branded!", undated (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - "The Brave Old Bull Fighter.", undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - "The Career of the Divorce-Court Detective.", undated (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - "Charity and Economy Combined."After Every Presidential Election, let All the Campaign Equipments be Distributed as Clothing Among the Homeless Wanderers of the Great City., undated (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - "The Charity Fiend.", undated (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - "A Cheerful Coaching."A Pastime that is not Quite Fully Naturalized as yet., undated (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - "Christmas Tips at the Country Club." The One Yearly Occasion When the Help Never Threatens to Leave.", undated (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - "Clear the Platform!"Independent Republican:-"Get off the front! I'm not going to carry any played-out old tramps any longer.", undated (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - "The Codfish Exodus to Europe.", undated (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - "A Cold Day for Prohibition."Prohibition Party.-Will it ever thaw out again?, undated (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - "Collapse of Another Buddensiek Structure."John Roach.-"It's all Whitney's fault. If he hadn't knocked so hard, it would be standing now.", undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - "`Coming Out' For Harrison."Protected Monopolist.- Chuck in your votes there, and don't forget that you're 'working for- Kane!', undated (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - "Cupid Modernized.", undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - "The Dead-Head Fiend.- A National Nuisance.", undated (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - "A Desperate Game.- But It Does N't Fool Anybody."Reid shouts "Democratic Frauds!"- while the Republican Forgery-Mill Grinds Merrily On., undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - "A Disastrous Skate.", undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - "Driven Into Exile.", undated (Box 3, Folder 181)